# Jonathan Fink

# **Full Stack Developer**

Los Angeles | (323) 337-6285 | Collegepulsemag@gmail.com www.code-with-jon.com | github.com/code-with-Jon | linkedin.com/jonathan-fink

# **Summary**

I am a Software Engineer who has spent the last seven years working in Business and Operations. Well versed in full-stack javascript, and React. I am known for my strong work ethic in both team and individual settings. I continue to expand my abilities as a full-stack developer, and push myself by building user facing projects.

#### **Skills**

HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | React | React Native | Node | Express | MongoDb | Mongoose | Java | Python | Jquery | Firebase | Amazon AWS | Django | SQL | Git & Version Control | API's | Eclipse | VSCode | Wordpress |

## **Projects**

### In Progress:

Steady Mobile Dating App (https://github.com/Code-With-Jon/Steady-Site)

- Using React Native, Redux, and Firebase to build a social dating app
- Incorporating matching algorithm, geolocation, and user inputs

#### completed:

Steady Mobile Dating App Website (https://github.com/Code-With-Jon/Steady-Site)

- Used MERN stack to build a supporting resource for Steady mobile app
- Implemented virtual assistant chat, Lottie animations, SMTP request to send email, and compatibility mini game

### MeetUp App (https://github.com/Code-With-Jon/Convene-2)

- CRUD application using Python, Django, HTML and CSS to build a meet up app similar to meetup.com
- Implemented AWS for storing photos on events

#### MineSweeper Clone (https://github.com/Code-With-Jon/MineSweeper)

- Used Vanilla JS, Jquery, HTML, and CSS to build a clone of the classic MineSweeper game
- Implemented Local Storage database to store previous durations of gameplay

#### AirBnB Clone (https://github.com/Code-With-Jon/AirB-LetB)

- CRUD application using EJS, Express, Mongo, Mongoose, HTML and CSS to build a clone of the base functionality of AirBnB.
- Implemented OAuth, User and Home Schema's, and incorporated both global and private views.

#### **Professional Experience**

#### Outreach Manager at Elements Real Estate | October 2016 – June 2018

- Designed and developed new enhancements to increase retention, gain better insight into KPI's, revised training procedures, and expanded potential client opportunity
- Developed and built new website features to include an offer submission section which enables the ability to store form and file information
- o Maintained and analyzed large data sets

#### Manager at Instacart | August 2015 – October 2016

- Led an 800 member team to consistently meet or exceed quality and efficiency goals
- o Delivered top-performing KPIs and metrics at multiple store locations
- o Owned performance management throughout the employee lifecycle

o Developed relationships resulting in improvements and cost savings for Instacart

# Outside Sales Representative at American Paper & Plastics | Aug 2012 - July 2015

- o Developed strong working knowledge of sales tactics and CRM software
- o Created lasting relationships with a large portfolio of clients

# Founder of COLLEGE PULSE MAGAZINE | January 2010 – March 2012

- o Demonstrated entrepreneurial spirit by founding and editing a collegiate magazine
- o Self-taught web design skills to create a portal for students to engage with CPM content

# **Education**

Santa Monica College | AA Business | Santa Monica, CA
California State University, Northridge | B.S Computer Science, In Progress\* | Los Angeles, CA
\*Hiatus to pursue professional ambitions and gain work experience
General Assembly | SEI | Santa Monica, CA